不
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不行 崔弗 不 行李必须全部塞进去 好吗?
No, Trevor, no. The bag has to go all the way in, okay?
充分利用空间 让一下 谢谢
Use all the space. Out the way. Thank you.
这里是怎么弄的啊?好吧
What's gone on back here? Right.
这个要搬过来 不然的话会到处乱窜的
These need to be moved around, 'cause this is gonna jiggle about, otherwise.
现在 我们要挪开...喂?
Now, can we move-- Hello?
这里还有人 天呐
There's someone in here. Oh, my God.
嘿 我差点忘了 你知道我们明天 要跟埃弗顿比赛吗?
Hey, almost forgot. You know how we're playing Everton tomorrow?
-知道 -那不是个城镇的名字
-Yeah. -Well, that's not a town.
-其实是在利物浦的一个球队! -就像披头士!
-It's actually a team in Liverpool! -Like the Beatles!
如果你见到保罗、乔治或是林戈 能拍个照吗?拜托了
If you see John, Paul, George or Ringo, will you take a picture, please?
没问题 小伙子
Hey, you got it, big guy.
好了 我要继续工作了 好吗?
Okay, hey, I better get a roll on here, all right?
好的 妈妈想跟你说话 先等一下
Okay. And Mom wants to talk to you. Hold on.
-我爱你 伙计 -我也爱你
-I love you, buddy. -Love you too.
你还没告诉他约翰和乔治已经死了?
Still haven't told him John and George are dead?
他们怎么了?
They're what?
是基思理查兹干的
It was Keith Richards.
嘿 泰德
Hey, Ted.
-嘿 你还好吗? -很好
-Hey. How you doing? -Good.
工作怎么样?一切都还好吗?
How's work going? Everything all right?
还好 抱歉 我知道这件事不容易 但律师寄过去的文件?
Yeah. I'm sorry. I know this isn't easy, but the paperwork the lawyer sent?
我知道 嘿
I know. Oh, hey.
在这儿呢
Got it right here.
我会看一遍 签上字 然后寄回去 我保证
I'll, uh, look it all over, sign it, send it right back. I promise.
好的 谢谢 嘿 祝你明天好运 我们会看比赛的
Okay, thanks. Hey, good luck tomorrow. We'll be watching.
好的
All right now.
(灿烂绽放花艺 纪念日快乐 瑞贝卡!)
(点击下方链接 享受八折订花)
-女生之旅! -利物浦 我们来了
-Girls' trip! -Mm. Liverpool, here we come.
我想提前说一下
I just want to say up front
你邀请我一起共度周末 我非常受宠若惊
that I'm really flattered you asked me to come this weekend.
拜托
Oh. Come on now.
但咱俩都是单身 我觉得你超级性感
But, hey, we're both single. I think you are super hot.
如果我要重新回到女同的市场上来
If I'm gonna dip my toe back into the lady pool,
我找不到比你更好的人选了
I can't think of a finer body of water to do it with than you.
不 基莉 我想你误会了
No. Keeley, I think you're confused.
我一开始是的 但后来我对自己说 “拜托 基莉
I was, at first. Then I was like, "Come on, Keeley.
放纵一下又何妨 跟你的新朋友好好爽一把”
Blow off some steam and have some wicked sex with your new friend."
我跟你开玩笑的
I'm fucking with you.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我以为你是认真的 你能想象吗?
I thought you were being serious. I mean, can you imagine?
哦 我想象过
Oh, I have.
看来今天的航班又多了一位乘客
Looks like we have a new passenger on today's flight.
其实 基莉会顶替 你在直升机上的位置 希金斯
Actually, Keeley will be taking your seat on the jet, Higgins.
抱歉
Sorry.
起飞前我先去上个厕所
I'm gonna go spend a penny before we take off.
楼下见 瑞贝卡
See you downstairs, Rebecca.
没关系 我一直很享受球队大巴上的胡闹
Oh, that's okay. I always enjoy the antics on the team bus.
不 我需要你周末留在这里
No. I need you to stay here this weekend.
做一些不重要的事
Doing work that doesn't matter.
好了 先生们 谁准备好 让埃弗顿见识我们的厉害了?
All right, gentlemen. Who's ready to go show Everton what we got?
谢谢 丹尼
Thank you, Dani.
天呐 路易斯 大家怎么都这么垂头丧气的?
Jeez, Louise. Why's everybody so down in the dumps?
出什么事了?碧昂丝甩了Jay-Z吗?
What happened? Did Beyoncé dump Jay-Z or something?
不 不是那样的
No, nothing like that.
谢天谢地 光是说说就让我很难过了
Thank goodness. Just saying it out loud made me immediately sad.
我看看是怎么回事
Let me see what's going on here.
嘿 伙计们 说真的 跟我聊聊 出什么事了?
Hey, guys. Seriously, come on. Talk to me. What's up?
我们挺好的
Well, we're fine.
-是啊 我没事 -好吧
-Yeah, I'm all right. -Okay.
我们心情差到爆 是因为我们从没赢过埃弗顿
We're in a shit fucking mood because we never fucking win at Everton
这真他妈让人郁闷!
and it sucks fucking shit!
拜托 伙计们
Ah, come on, fellas.
你们上一次赢埃弗顿是多久之前?
How long has it been since y'all won up at Everton?
-60年前 -老天
-Sixty years ago. -Jesus Christ.
哇 这也太久了吧 好吧
Wow. That is a heck of a long time. Okay.
所以大家担心的是这个
So we got that going on.
显然欧布莱恩拉伤了屁股这事 让我们大家都很失望
And obviously we're bummed out that O'Brien tore his butt.
是上腘绳肌肌腱 教练
It's my upper hamstring, Coach.
你拉伤了屁股 孩子 没什么丢脸的 好吗?这种事常有
You tore your butt, son. There's nothing to be ashamed of, okay? It happens.
运动员经常会拉伤屁股 你不是一个人 伙计
People tear their butts all the time in athletics. You're not alone, man.
嘿 教练 你也拉伤过好几次 对吗?
Hey, Coach, you've torn your butt a few times, right?
-三次 -三次
-Three times. -Three times.
屁股是很了不起的肌肉 上帝作证 你的屁股会好起来的
Butt's an amazing muscle. God as my witness, your butt will heal.
虽然欧布莱恩拉伤了屁股 但好的一面是
The silver lining here, with O'Brien's tore butt,
我这位来自蒙特利尔的朋友 会顶替守门员的位置
is that my man from Montreal is gonna be filling in at goalie.
-大家欢迎佐罗 -发音是“佐豪”
-Give it up for Zorro. -Oh. It's pronounced, um, "Zoreaux."
-抱歉 佐罗 -“佐豪”
-I'm sorry. Zorro. -"Zoreaux."
我不知道我哪念错了
You-- I don't know what I'm doing wrong here.
重点是 先生们 除非你们当中有人有水晶球
Point is, gentlemen, unless one of y'all got a crystal ball,
我们不知道明天会发生什么
we don't know what's gonna happen tomorrow.
所以我们才要比赛
That's why we play the game.
让我听到你们的决心!里士满数到三! 一、二、三!
So let me hear it! Richmond on three! One, two, three!
-里士满! -好了 我们走吧
-Richmond! -Right, come on. Let's go.
-嘿 教练 -你们好 伙计们 有什么事吗?
-Hey, Coach. -Howdy, fellas. How can I help you?
既然杰米塔特已经回到曼城
Um, so, uh, since Jamie Tartt has gone back to Man City,
你们输了一场 打平了一场 你们还没进过球
uh, you've lost one, you've drawn one, you've not scored any goals.
-是的 -所以我想知道
-Yeah. -So I'm wondering,
你对球队降级这件事有多担忧?
how worried are you about the threat of relegation?
劳埃德 现在我最关心的是降级的定义
Lloyd, right now I'm mostly concerned with the definition of relegation.
你有什么问题问我 马库斯?
What you got for me, Marcus?
就是想知道你对杰米塔特的离去作何感想
Just wanted to know how you're feeling about the departure of Jamie Tartt.
这个
Yeah. Um...
说实话 这让我有一点伤心
Well, if I'm being honest, it, uh, breaks my heart a little.
我认为对教练而言最有趣的事莫过于
I think one of the neatest things about being a coach
和你的球员建立的情感纽带
is the connection you get to make with your players.
相比球场上比赛时会发生的事 他的离去对我的打击更重
That's a loss that hits me a lot harder and is gonna stay with me a lot longer
我也需要更久的时间来释怀
than anything that happens while playing a game on a patch of grass.
好了 我们利物浦见了 好吗?
All right. See you fellas in Liverpool, yeah?
好的
Yeah.
嘿!最后一个到的是苏格兰煮蛋!
Oh. Hey! Last one there is a Scotch egg! Whoo!
什么?
What?
嘿 他在这儿呢
Hey, there he is.
-很高兴见到你 伙计 -好了 走吧
-Good to see you, buddy. -All right, let's go.
到了 这是总统套房 希望您能满意
Here we go. It's the presidential suite. Hope it's to your satisfaction.
需要我为您介绍房间的便利设施吗?
Would you like me to show you the various room amenities?
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
我和我女人想在今晚去镇上之前
My lady and I wanna have a quick shag and a shower
赶紧来一发 然后洗个澡
before we hit the town tonight.
欢迎来到利物浦
Welcome to Liverpool.
怎么了?给小费的话 他一分钟不到就会花光的
What? He would've spent a cash tip in, like, a minute.
拜托 那个画面会印在他脑海里一辈子的
Come on. The image I just gave him is gonna last for a lifetime.
不 不是你的问题 而是...该死
No, it's-- it's not you. It's-- Oh, fuck.
今天是我和鲁伯特的周年纪念 而且...
This is Rupert's and my anniversary weekend. And--
-这是我第一个独自度过的纪念日... -嘿 没事的
-It's the first one I've spent by myself-- -Hey, it's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
好久的拥抱
-Mm. -Ooh. That's a long hug.
好了 提醒一下大家 酒店房间的家具不准移动
So, just to remind you, the hotel furniture stays in the rooms,
不能移到走廊或是游泳池
not the hallway or the pool.
也不能快递寄回家 或是寄到其他酒店 好吗?
Nor are you allowed to ship it to your homes or other hotels, okay?
好了 伙计们 一小时后团队聚餐
All right, fellas, we got team meal in an hour.
在那之后 我们可以度过一个电影之夜 或是枕头大战
After that, it's either gonna be movie night or a pillow fight.
你们选什么?
What's it gonna be this time around?
电影之夜
Movie night.
好吧 但我跟你们讲 你们只要说一次“枕头大战”
All right. But I tell you what, y'all say "pillow fight" one time,
以后就再也不会想一起看电影了
and we'll never watch another movie together again.
-这是给你的 教练 -谢谢
-That's for you, Coach. -Thank you, sir.
-这是给你的 -谢谢
-And that's for you. -Thank you.
5150号房间 终于等到你
Whoo! Room 5150. Finally.
山米海格 范海伦乐队历史上最伟大的主唱
Sammy Hagar, greatest lead singer in Van Halen history.
-在大卫李罗斯之后 -谢谢
-In the post-David Lee Roth era. -Thank you.
-教练 你住几号房? -5148
-Coach, what room you got? -5148.
-嘿 -你好啊 邻居
-Hey. -Howdy, neighbor.
你好 我们叫的香槟还没送来 谢谢
Yes, hello. We still haven't received the champagne I ordered. Thank you.
问得好 稍等一下
Ah. Good question. One second.
我应该让礼宾部 给我们定一个晚餐的位子吗?
Should I get the concierge to make us a reservation somewhere tonight?
就食物和氛围而言 希普里牛排屋最赞了
Shipley's steak house is unmatched in its cuisine and ambience.
是吗?好的 牛排我爱吃
Mm. Is it now? Cool, I can do steak.
是的 牛排店两位 谢谢
Uh, yes. The steak house for two, please.
晚上8点你可以吗?
Does 8:00 p.m. work for you?
商业中心24小时营业
The business center is open 24 hours a day.
好吧
Okay.
你刚才说商业中心是什么意思?
What was that about the business center?
客人还可以享受我们最高端的健身房
Guests also have access to our state-of-the-art gym,
其中应用了最新的健身科技
filled with the latest in workout technology.
比如说壶铃!
Like kettlebells!
我的天
Oh, my God.
夜晚的利物浦比白天更热闹非凡
Liverpool has much to offer when it comes to nightlife.
从酒吧到俱乐部 到亚洲人打发闲暇时光的利器卡拉OK!
From pubs and clubs, to the great Asian pastime of karaoke!
我都不记得拍过这个了
I don't even remember doing this.
-如果你追求艺术... -好吧 够了
-And if you're the artsy type-- -Right, enough.
这个周末我们要向前看
This weekend is moving forward.
等香槟到了 我们大醉一场 好好吃一顿
When that champagne arrives, we are going to get drunk, have a nice meal,
然后把过去抛在脑后
and leave the past in the past.
-听上去不错吧? -听上去好极了
-Sound good? -Sounds fucking great.
说曹操曹操到
Oh. Speak of the devil.
你好 讨厌鬼
Hello, Stinky.
没有鲁伯特那个老家伙买单 他们还是给了你一个大房间
Still giving you the big room even without old gray walnuts footing the bill.
很好 去他的鲁伯特!
Good. Fuck Rupert!
这是谁?是你的情妇吗?俄罗斯人?
Oh. Who's this then? Is this your concubine? Is she Russian?
-你是俄罗斯人吗? -首先 我喜欢你 其次 你是谁?
-Are you Russian? -A, I love you. B, who are you?
我给你介绍一下 这是弗洛柯林斯 我们从小就是闺蜜
Let me introduce Flo Collins, my best mate since we were little.
杰出的儿童心理学家 一个骄傲的新晋单身母亲
Brilliant child psychologist and proud, newly single...
她12岁的女儿诺拉 是我见过的最棒的小女孩 也是我的教女
Mm-hmm.
...mother to the most amazing 12-year-old little girl called Nora, my goddaughter.
哇
Wow.
过去的六年里 我完全忽视了她们俩 一次都没有联系过
Both of whom I've completely neglected to speak to in the last six years.
老天 讨厌鬼
Oh, Jesus, Stinky.
记得提醒我把你放进我葬礼的发言名单里
Remind me to bury you in the set list for speeches at my funeral.
嗨 我叫弗洛 你可以叫我"靓女” 你叫哪个都行
Hi, I'm Flo. Or you can call me "Sassy." I don't care which.
所以 你听说了离婚的事?
So, you heard about the divorce?
是啊 我那天在派对上遇见了达伦 他跟我搭讪后告诉我的
Yeah. I bumped into Derren at a party. He told me right after he hit on me.
嘿 这一点不新鲜 不过 他告诉你这件事 还是很奇怪
Hey, what's new? Still, weird order for him to roll out that information.
好吧 今晚有什么计划?
Right, what's in the plan for tonight, then?
我应该打个电话?让他们送件浴袍过来?
Shall I call down? Get myself a robe?
看看我带了什么
Look what I've got.
从外面一个房间服务推车里顺走的
Stole it off a room service trolley outside.
你真棒!
You're amazing!
对了 我叫基莉 嗨!
-I'm Keeley, by the way. Hi! -Oh!
是的 我知道你是谁 亲爱的
Yeah, I know who you are, honey.
我前夫经常像个疯子一样 对着你的照片打飞机 所以...
My ex used to masturbate to you like a maniac, so...
我要是认为我们明天能打败他们 是不是疯了?
Am I cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs thinking we can beat these guys tomorrow?
-不 我们势均力敌 -就是说啊
-No, we match up perfectly. -Exactly.
你呢 内特?你相信我们能赢吗?
What about you, Nate? You believe these guys can win?
我认为这支队伍能做到任何事
I believe this team can do anything.
瞧?这就对了 要的就是这个精神
See? There you go. That's what I'm talking about.
好的 内特 如果你是我 你会怎么跟球员说?
Okay, Nate. So if you were me, what would you tell these guys?
不 我不能...不行 我...
Oh, no. I wouldn't-- No, I don't--
嘿 我只是问你意见 你明白的吧?
Hey. I'm just asking for your opinion. You understand that, yeah?
-嗯 -你想到了什么 对吗?
-Yeah. -And you got one, yes?
-对 -子弹上膛 就等一鸣惊人了?
-Yeah. -Locked, loaded, ready to rip?
-说来听听 -不
-Let me hear it. -No.
为什么不行? 你害怕告诉我之后会发生什么?
Why not? What are you afraid's gonna happen if you tell me?
害怕你不会喜欢我的想法 害怕你会讨厌我
That you won't like my idea and it makes you hate me.
然后开除我
Then you fire me.
然后我只能搬回父母家 被他们看不起
Then I have to move back in with my parents and they'll be ashamed of me.
然后所有人都会知道我回了老家 并嘲笑我 直到我没脸见人
Then everyone finds out back home and laughs at me until my face melts off.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
至少他这次没结巴
Well, at least he didn't stammer.
(米歇尔拉索)
(抱歉打搅你 能抽空看下那个文件吗?亲亲)
我有些事要处理 明早见 好吗?
I gotta go take care of a couple things. I'll see you in the morning, all right?
嘿 帮我个忙 照看一下这些家伙
Hey, do me a favor. Keep an eye on these guys,
因为电影演到74分钟的时候 会有一屋子的大男人泣不成声的
'cause around the 74 minute mark, there's gonna be a room full of grown men crying.
我会是其中之一
I'll be one of 'em.
好吧 所以我什么都没准备
Right, so I hadn't prepared anything.
对于一个伴娘来说不是什么好主意 尤其是酒水免费
Not the brightest idea for a maid of honor, especially with an open bar.
是的 她是周末之星
Yeah, she was the star of the weekend.
-是的 我让埃尔顿约翰勃起了 -你做了什么?
-Yeah, I gave Elton John a boner. -You did what?
-不 你没有 -我有!
-No, you didn't. -Yes, I did!
他总是否认
He has repeatedly denied that.
经典的“自相矛盾” 不是吗?
Ah. Classic "she said, she said," innit?
女士们 还要开一瓶吗? 来点甜品怎么样?
Would you ladies like another bottle? A little dessert perhaps?
我这位性感的、单身单到发霉的朋友
My sexy and extremely single friend here
事实上想要的是另一种甜品
actually prefers her desserts on the larger side.
如果你能安排一下最好了
If that's something you could possibly accommodate.
我给你们几分钟时间
I'll give you a few minutes.
谢谢 抱歉
Thank you. Sorry.
真不敢相信你居然那么说了
I can't believe you just did that.
闭嘴啦 我知道你喜欢
Oh, shut up. You love it.
好了 我要去抽支烟 讨厌鬼?
Right. I'm going for a smoke. Stinky?
不了 我已经戒了
No. Don't smoke anymore.
但是你这把火还是烧得很旺啊
And yet, you're still on fire.
嗯 我不知道 只是...
Yeah, I don't know. Just--
我建议您再冲一次 再用力一些 好 再见
May I suggest flushing it again but harder? Okay, bye.
嗨 有什么需要帮忙的?
Hi, how can I help you?
嘿 你好吗?我想问一下 你们有没有传真机
Hey, how you doing? I was wondering if y'all had a fax machine.
传真机?
Fax machine?
好的 这是个好问题 请给我一点时间
Oh, okay. Um, that's a good question. If you bear with me a second,
我问下我的同事看看能找到什么
I'll just check with a colleague and see what I can find out.
传真机 嘿?你是要发什么到1997年吗?
A fax machine, hey? Are you sending something to the year 1997?
是啊 就是给自己的一点提示 提醒那时的我买苹果的股票
Yeah, just a little note to myself telling me to buy Apple stock.
好主意
Oh. Good idea.
你能顺便告诉那时的我杀掉JK洛琳 然后自己写第一本《哈利波特》吗?
Can you tell me to murder J.K. Rowling and write the first Harry Potter book as well?
没问题 我可能会写“除掉”而不是“杀掉”
Can do. Yeah. I'll probably write "handle" instead of "murder,"
这样不会留下证据
so there's no paper trail.
-对了 我叫泰德 -靓女
-Yeah, I'm Ted, by the way. -Oh. Sassy.
靓女?就像蓝精灵 是吗?
Sassy, huh? Like the Smurf, right?
我不觉得有靓女蓝精灵这个角色 对吗?
Don't think there was a Sassy Smurf, was there?
太可惜了
That's too bad.
如果蓝精灵有个性的话 一定很有趣
Seems like a Smurf with an attitude would've been a lot of fun to watch.
好的 我会跟他说的 你试过之后告诉我结果 好的 再见
All right, yeah, I'll tell him. Let me know how the trial goes. Okay, bye.
好的 我们这里没有传真机
Right, we no longer have a fax machine on the premises.
但是礼宾部在13公里外的克蒂斯
But the concierge was able to locate one
的一家美黑沙龙里找到了一台
at a tanning salon eight miles away in Croxteth.
没关系
You know what, that's okay.
我去问问附近那个养信鸽的美甲师好了
I'm just gonna hit this manicurist nearby that has carrier pigeons.
-不过谢谢你 -好的
-Thank you though. All right. -Okay.
很高兴认识你
Nice meeting you.
好的 有什么需要帮忙的?
Right, how can I help you?
我是打算出去抽支烟
Well, I was gonna go out for a smoke
希望我朋友趁我不在的时候能把账结了
and hope my friend picks up the check while I was gone.
结果发现了这位马格南侦探 我心想跟他调个情也无妨
Then I saw Magnum, P.I. in line, figured I'd flirt with him as well.
-看看会发生什么 你知道吗? -祝你好运
-See what happens, you know? -Oh, well, good luck.
是啊 我好像搞砸了
Yeah, I think I fucked it.
事实上 我再过半个小时就换班了 如果你想...
I-- I actually get off in about 30 minutes if you'd like to, uh--
当然不会 你怎么会看上我?
Of course not, why would you?
你可以选择成为什么样的人
You are who you choose to be.
超人
Superman.
我刚刚竟然遇见了 万宝路香烟盒上的男人...
Okay, so I just met the fucking Marlboro Man in the--
-讨厌鬼去哪了?她抛弃你了? -没有 她去尿尿了
-Where's Stinky gone? She abandoned you? -No, she just went to pee.
你为什么叫她“讨厌鬼”?
-Oh. -Where does "Stinky" come from?
我还记得她搬到我们镇上的那天
I remember the day she moved into our town.
她那时就比我高了 穿着一双大码的鞋
She was already taller than me, had bigger boobs.
她家很有钱 所以七年级第一天上课时
Family was rich. So, first day of year seven,
我告诉所有人她的外号叫“讨厌鬼”
I told everyone her nickname was "Stinky."
太天才了
That's genius.
敬让我们相连的羁绊
To the ties that bind us.
敬瑞贝卡
To Rebecca.
好吧 那不是瑞贝卡
Yeah, that's not Rebecca.
什么意思?
How do you mean?
真正的瑞贝卡是个傻瓜
No, the real Rebecca is silly.
很强大 但不是这样冷冰冰的
Strong, yeah, but not cold.
-你听过她唱歌吗? -没有
-Have you ever heard her sing? -No.
她的嗓音很美妙
Ah. Beautiful voice.
她和诺拉会唱上几小时 从门外就能听见
Her and Nora would sing through the door for hours.
你想不想堆个雪人?
Do you wanna build a snowman?
-诺拉是谁? -我女儿
-Who's Nora? -My daughter.
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
如果你喜欢那个女人 你一定会爱上瑞贝卡
Yeah, if you like that woman, you are gonna love Rebecca.
-可以走了吗? -账单怎么办?
-Ready? -What about the bill?
-谢谢 韦尔顿女士 -好的
-Thank you, Miss Welton. -Okay.
你要不要演假装要付钱的戏码?
Do you wanna do that thing where you pretend you wanted to pay?
是的 这会很有趣的 一起来
Oh, yeah, yeah. This is really good fun. Join in.
你这个混球!我本来打算付钱的
Oh, you absolute piece of shit! I was about to do that!
-我刚想把银行卡拿出来 -真不敢相信你居然偷偷付了钱
-I was just about to get my card out. -I can't believe that you've done this.
-我们平摊吧 你太好了 -我等了六年才等到...
-We were gonna split. That was so nice. -Six years I've waited for this...
(离婚协议书)
(米歇尔拉索 悉奥多拉索)
(我是布莱恩斯旺森 米歇尔的律师 她要我联系你)
(好消息!你可以将签好的文件拍照 发邮件过来即可)
-你在干什么? -对不起 我只是...
-What the hell are you doing? -I'm-- I'm so sorry. I just--
你什么?
You're what?
-这是什么? -这是我对球队的想法
-What is this? -It's just my thoughts on the team.
走吧 内森 拜托 已经过了宵禁时间
Go, Nathan. Come on, it's past curfew.
-快走!离开这里! -抱歉
-Go! Get outta here! -Sorry.
夜晚的利物浦比白天更热闹非凡
Liverpool has much to offer when it comes to nightlife.
从酒吧到俱乐部 到亚洲人打发闲暇时光的利器卡拉OK!
From pubs and clubs, to the great Asian pastime of karaoke!
如果你追求艺术 或者你只是想打动约会对象
And if you're the artsy type, or you're just trying to impress a date,
利物浦的博物馆和画廊...
Liverpool has more museums and galleries...
欢迎来到古迪逊公园 我是阿尔洛怀特 和克里斯鲍威尔一起解说
Welcome to Goodison Park. I'm Arlo White here with Chris Powell.
好了 伙计们!来吃点零食吧!
-Okay, guys! Got some snacks here! -Whoo-hoo!
尽量别在上半场就吃光了 加油 里士满!
Let's try not to eat them all in the first half. Come on, Richmond!
排在第八位的埃弗顿主场对阵AFC里士满
It's eighth-place Everton hosting AFC Richmond,
后者排在18位 并且面临降级的风险
in 18th and staring relegation in the face.
上一次里士满赢得比赛的时候
The last time Richmond left here with a win,
英国最火的歌是猫王的《把握现在》
the number one song in the UK was by Elvis Presley, "It's Now or Never."
对泰德拉索的球员而言 这正是今晚的写照
And that's certainly the case for Ted Lasso's men tonight.
-内特 我能跟你说几句吗? -好
-Nate, can I speak with you, please? -Yeah.
你没事吧?
You all right?
我想为昨晚的事跟你道歉 我无缘无故冲你发脾气
I wanted to apologize for last night. I bit your head off for no good reason,
我真的很抱歉 希望你能原谅我
and I'm really sorry about that and I hope you can forgive me.
当然 我当然会原谅你
Yeah, of cour-- Yes, of course.
谢谢 还有 我看了你的建议
Thank you. Also, I read through your thoughts.
-好的 -我觉得非常好
-Yeah. -They're great.
上面的每一句话我都赞同
And I agree with every last one of 'em.
但我不能跟球队说
But I can't say this to them.
-但他们需要听到这番话 -我同意
-But they need to hear it. -I agree.
所以你来说
That's why you're gonna do it.
你喝醉了吗?
Are you drunk?
你来做赛前演讲 你来读这些话
You're giving the pregame talk, and you're gonna read them this.
-不太好吧 -会很有意思的
-I ju-- I don't know. -It'll be fun.
不
No. No, no, no.
天呐
Oh, my God.
好了 听好了 伙计们
All right, listen up, fellas.
最近我觉得你们已经听够了我的碎碎念
As of late, I feel like y'all have heard enough of my jibber-jabber.
所以我让伟大的内特来分享一些
So I asked Nate the Great here to jot down a few of his thoughts and ideas
他对你们和今天的比赛的一些想法和建议
about you guys and today's game.
大家认真听
So let's focus up.
-交给你了 内特 -好的
-All yours, Nate. -Okay.
-说吧 内特 -加油 伙计 你可以的
-Let's go, Nate. -Come on, boy. You got this.
-你可以的 内特 没事的 -好的 谢谢 我开始了
-You got this, Nate. It's okay. -Okay. Thank you. Let's do it.
艾萨克
-Isaac. -Hmm?
好了 你没问题的 老兄 对吗?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah, you got this, bruv, all right?
没错
Yeah.
我发现最近...
I've noticed of late...
你在场上的表现就像一个没长脑子的孬种
that you've been playing like a big, dumb pussy.
哇
Wow.
你他妈说什么 老兄?
What the fuck did you say to me, bruv?
你更关注外表强悍 而不是真的强悍
You're more concerned about looking tough than actually being tough.
不是只有靠武力才能震慑住对方
There's a way to be intimidating without being physical.
我希望你不介意我这么说
I hope you don't mind me saying.
-山姆 -哦 不
-Sam. -Oh, no.
你总是在两翼失球
You're constantly getting beat on the wings.
因为你犹豫不决
It's 'cause you're indecisive.
你的二次判断就像是不称职的灵媒
You second-guess more than a shitty psychic.
我知道的唯一一个 比你更受困于自己思想的黑人
The only African I know more imprisoned by their own thoughts
就是该死的奈尔森曼德拉
is goddamn Nelson Mandela.
你听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
你觉得很好笑吗 科林? 你和你那花哨的“踩单车”谁都骗不到
You think that's funny, do you, Colin? You and all your fancy step over bullshit.
我问你一个问题 你给下面脱毛吗?
Let me ask you this. Do you wax your pubes?
什么?
What?
我口吃了吗 混蛋? 你给下面脱毛吗?有还是没有
Did I stutter, dickhead? Do you wax your pubes? Yes or no.
没有
No.
那你干嘛总表现得像个巴西人?
Then why are you always trying to play like a Brazilian?
是吧
Yeah.
刚才发生了什么?
What just happened?
-罗哈斯 -侮辱我吧 朋友
-Uh, Rojas. -Whoo! Roast me, amigo.
好的 你说“足球就是生命” 对吗?
All right. You say that football is life, right?
足球就是生命
Football is life.
那你的防守就是找死
-Yeah, well, then your defense is death. -Oh!
我知道的唯一一个比你更守不住男人的 是该死的卡莉布拉德肖
The only person I've seen lose their man more often is Carrie fucking Bradshaw.
《欲望都市》
-Sex and the City. -Shh.
-是吧 -话糙理不糙
-Yeah. -Tough but fair.
好了 罗伊
Right. Roy.
继续 说你想说的
Go on. Say what you're gonna say.
好的
Okay.
不要念稿子
Don't read it.
看着我的脸说
Say it to my face.
伟大的罗伊肯特
The great Roy Kent.
你现在老了
You're old now.
而且更慢了 你常常溜号
And slow. And your focus drifts.
但造就你的从来不是 你的速度和你的小聪明
But your speed and your smarts were never what made you who you are.
是你的愤怒 那才是你的超能力
It's your anger. That's your superpower.
那让你成为联赛历史上 最优秀的中场球员之一
That's what made you one of the best midfielders in the history of this league.
但在我本季的赛场上完全没看到 罗伊
But I haven't seen it on the pitch at all this season, Roy.
过去的你奔跑时的样子 都像是对草充满愤怒
I mean, you used to run like you were angry at the grass.
你踢球的力度就像是 逮到它跟你老婆偷情 老天
You'd kick the ball like you'd caught it fucking your wife, for Christ's sake.
但那种愤怒再也见不到了
But that anger doesn't come out anymore when you play.
但它仍然在你身体里
But it's still in there.
你把所有怒气都憋在心里 这会对你造成怎样的伤害 我很担心
And I'm afraid of what it's gonna do to you if you just keep it all for yourself.
我们去打败那群混蛋
Let's go get these fuckers.
瞧?我告诉过你会很有趣
See? Told you it'd be fun.
不可能的事情发生了 里士满一比零赢了埃弗顿
And the impossible has happened. Richmond have won at Everton 1-0.
-太好了 泰德!好耶! -多亏了罗伊肯特罕见的一球
-Yes, Ted! Yeah! -Thanks to a rare goal from Roy Kent.
昆特今天的表现十分出色 他像是被附身了一样
Kent was absolutely brilliant today. He was like a man possessed.
耶!
Yeah!
铭记于心 不曾怀疑
We know we are, we're sure we are.
我们是里士满 至死不渝 我们是里士满...
We're Richmond till we die. We're Richmond...
老天!
Oh, my God!
过来拥抱一下 内特 太好了
Come on, give us a hug, Nate. Yeah.
-泰德! -嘿!
-Ted! -Hey!
-恭喜 -谢谢 老板
-Congratulations. -Thanks, boss.
我能介绍你认识...
Could I, uh, just introduce you to--
-靓女蓝精灵! -万宝路男!天呐
-Sassy Smurf! -Marlboro Man! Oh, my God.
铭记于心 不曾怀疑...
We know we are, we're sure we are...
-我不知道你也在 -惊喜!
-I didn't know you were here. -Surprise!
我这个周末经常想起你
I've been thinking about you a lot this weekend.
是吗?怎么会?
Oh, yeah? How come?
因为我一打开电视 你就会顶着那个疯狂的发型蹦出来
'Cause you and your crazy hair keep popping up every time I turn on my TV.
喂!听好了!
Oi! Listen up!
今晚谁都不准回酒店
None of you are going back to the hotel tonight.
因为我们今天做了出乎所有人意料的事 甚至包括我们自己!
'Cause we did something today that no one thought we could do, including us!
所以我们要出去 我们要庆祝
So, we're going out, we're celebrating,
我们要戳这座城市的痛点
and we're gonna rub it in this city's fucking face!
罗伊!我们去哪?
Roy! Roy! Where are we going?
基莉?
Keeley?
利物浦热闹非凡
Well, Liverpool has much to offer.
从酒吧到俱乐部 到亚洲人打发闲暇时光的...
From pubs to clubs to the great Asian pastime of...
-我说了也许 -也许
-I said maybe -Said maybe
你会是那个拯救我的人
You're gonna be the one that saves me
拯救我
Saves me
毕竟
And after all
你是我的奇迹
You're my wonderwall
我去抽支烟
I'm going for a smoke.
-我可以一起吗? -来吧
-Can I join you? -Come on.
谢谢 里士满FC!
Thank you, Richmond FC!
万宝路男是怎么回事?
So, what's Marlboro Man's story, then?
因为我有点想拽着他的耳朵
'Cause I kinda wanna grab him by the ears
像骑水上摩托车那样骑他
and ride that little mustache like a Jet Ski.
-见到你太高兴了 靓女 -我也是 讨厌鬼
-It's so good to see you, Sass. -You too, Stinky.
天呐 你知道 今天是我的...
God. You know, today would've been my--
我当然知道了 不然你觉得我为什么会来?
Of course I know. Why do you think I'm here?
姐们 我很抱歉
Mate, I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉从你和诺拉的生活中消失了
I'm sorry for disappearing from you, from Nora.
真的
I really am.
谢谢你这么说
Thank you for saying that.
天呐 那个男人夺走了我太多东西
God, that man took so much from me.
不
No.
鲁伯特是一个很可怕的人 他建了一座象牙塔把你囚禁在里面
Rupert is a horrible man who built an ivory tower he kept you captive in.
但是你靠自己一步一步从塔里爬了出来
But you climbed every single step of that tower on your own.
是你不再回到那个家 不再打电话
You're the one who stopped coming home, stopped calling.
是你让一个六岁的女孩思索 她到底哪里做错了
Who made a six-year-old girl wonder what she'd done wrong.
我会永远守护你
I'll always be your biggest defender,
但你必须承认你做错的事
but you have to own up to the part that you played.
你说得对
You're right.
我当然是对的 我总是对的
Course I'm right. I'm always right.
你不总是对的 大部分时候你就是个混蛋
You're not always right. Most of the time you're an arse.
你们在这儿呢 该死的 我以为你们抛弃了我
There you are. Fucking hell. I thought you guys ditched me.
-没有 -怎么会!
-No! -As if!
天呐 在此之前我都不知道 我会这么害怕被抛弃
Jesus, I didn't know that I had abandonment issues till right now.
走吧 瑞贝卡 下一首是你的歌
Come on, Rebecca. Your song's up next.
-什么? -是啊
-What? -Yeah.
不 我没有选歌
No, I didn't put a song in.
那肯定是别人帮你选好了
Well, then someone else must've done it for you.
会是谁呢?
Who could've done that?
瞧?你就是个混蛋
See? You are an arse.
被坏坏的浪漫困住了
Caught in a bad romance
啊-啊-啊-啊-啊 浪-漫-浪-漫-漫
Ra-ra-ah-ah-ah Roma-roma-ma
嘎嘎 哦 啦啦！
Gaga, ooh-la-la
想要你坏坏的浪漫
Want your bad romance
好了 下一个是谁?
All right, who's next?
我
Me, me, me.
轮到你了 瑞贝卡 上来
Your turn, Rebecca. Get on up here.
谢谢 天呐
Thank you. Oh, God.
好吧 我都不知道我要唱什么歌
Okay. Uh, I don't even know what song I'm singing.
但我想把这首歌献给我最好的朋友
But I would like to dedicate it to the best friend a girl could ever have.
是我!她说的是我!
That is me! She's talking about me!
也把这首歌献给我的教女诺拉
This is also dedicated to my goddaughter, Nora.
我爱你
I love you.
白雪发亮 今夜铺满山上
The snow glows white On the mountain tonight
没有脚印的地方
Not a footprint to be seen
孤立的王国很荒凉 我是这里的女皇
A kingdom of isolation And it looks like I'm the queen
风在呼啸 像心里的风暴一样
The wind is howling Like this swirling storm inside
只有天知道 我受过的伤
Couldn't keep it in Heaven knows I've tried
别让他们进来看见 做好女孩就像你的从前
Don't let them in, don't let them see Be the good girl you always have to be
躲藏不让他们看见
Conceal, don't feel Don't let them know
已被发现
Well, now they know
随它吧 随它吧
Let it go, let it go
回头已没有办法
Can't hold it back anymore
随它吧 随它吧
Let it go, let it go
一转身不再牵挂
Turn away and slam the door
我不管他们想说的话
I don't care what they're going to say
任风吹雨打
Let the storm rage on
反正冰天雪地我也不怕
The cold never bothered me anyway
-泰德 -爸爸?
-Ted. -Dad?
泰德？
Ted?
泰德
Ted.
没事了
It's okay.
试着呼吸
Try to breathe.
我不行 我不知道这是怎么了 对不起
I can't. I don't know what's going on. I'm-- I'm sorry.
没事了 你惊恐发作了 呼吸
It's okay. You're having a panic attack. Just breathe.
我疯了吗?
Am I going crazy?
不会比其他人更疯
No more than anyone else.
好了 你没事了
All right. You're all right.
就是这样 很好
There we go. There we go. There we go. Come on.
很好
Come on.
就是这样
There we go.
我想我得先走了
I think I need to call it a night.
我要回酒店好好睡一觉
Gonna go back to the hotel and just get a good night's rest, you know?
需要我陪你走回去吗?
Would you like me to walk back with you?
你想开我的车吗?
Do you want to take my car?
不 不用了 谢谢你 我很感激
No, no, no. I'm okay. Thank you though. I appreciate it.
-好吧 -好了
-All right. -Okay.
嘿 帮我个忙 告诉彼尔德我回酒店了
Hey, do me a favor. Just, uh, let Beard know I went back to the hotel.
当然 你路上小心
Of course. You just get home safely.
-好的 谢谢你 -好
-Okay, thank you. -All right.
好的
Okay.
-不好意思 醉汉借过 -是的
-Excuse me. Very drunk man coming through. -Yeah.
伙计们 我想我们应该带大家去酒吧
Guys. Guys, guys, guys. I think we should take the boys to the pub.
我太累了 靓女 抱歉
Oh, I am so done, Sass. Sorry.
我今晚也到此为止了
Think I'm tapping out for the evening too, actually.
所以我要一个人 带着18个年轻帅气的男人去酒吧?
So I have to take 18 young, handsome men all by myself?
真是难为你了
Oh, trauma.
-好吧 再见 -再见 我爱你
-All right then. See you later. -Bye. I love you.
朋友们 我找不到我的热带衬衫了
Amigos, I can't find my tropical shirt.
-他醉得太厉害了 -我们不需要的 你不需要的
-He's so drunk. -You won't need it, you won't need it.
好了 要搭个便车回酒店吗?
Right, want a lift back to the hotel?
不用了 我想我还是走回去吧
Oh, no. Um, I think I'm gonna walk, actually.
除非你想跟我一起走 这我倒是可以
Unless you want me to come with you, 'cause that I can do.
-我没事 真的 -是吗?
-I'm fine. Really. -Yeah?
而且 纪念日已经是昨天了
Besides, that was yesterday.
-你在浪费宝贵的时间 -是啊 我走了
-You're wasting valuable time. -Yeah, yeah. I'm going, I'm going.
这是我的房间
Oh, this is me.
我跟瑞贝卡共享一个套房 不过我们的卧室是分开的
I'm sharing a suite with Rebecca. We've got separate bedrooms though.
晚安
Good night.
(泰德拉索-谢谢你这么好心 不仅是今晚)
(我们一路走来 你一直如此 这很难得)
字幕翻译:肖雪